<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Exlicit2</string>

    <string name="mypara">Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam</string>

<string name="mypara2">dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48dmit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exam. Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48</string>

    <string name="mypara1.5"> Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exa Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exa Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exa Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exa Admit Card will be available for download through Candidate login only 24 to 48 hrs prior to Date of Exa </string>


</resources>
